Guide to the Yale Events and Activities Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs of events and activities, 1852-1974; Series I
  - The Negro at Yale (Box 32, Folder 527)
  - Negro students, 1950-1956 (Box 32, Folder 528)
  - New Buildings, 1953-1964 (Box 32, Folder 529)
  - New Haven
    - Arts Festival (Box 32, Folder 530)
    - College (Box 32, Folder 531)
    - Development (Box 32, Folder 532)
    - Railroad (Box 32, Folder 533)
  - News Board, 1966-1969 (Box 32, Folder 534)
  - News Bureau, Yale University, Circa 1950-1963 (Box 32, Folder 535 - 536)
  - New York Free University, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 537)
  - Northern Student Movement (Box 33, Folder 538)
  - Oil Drilling, 1901 (Box 33, Folder 539)
  - Old Campus (Box 33, Folder 540)
  - "Operation Match" (Box 33, Folder 541)
  - Orchestra and Concert groups (Box 33, Folder 542)
  - Organizations, 1910- 1911 (Box 33, Folder 543)
  - Painting, "Regnor" by Stanley Roseman (Box 33, Folder 544)
  - Parade, Columbus Day, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 545)
  - Park Plaza Hotel (Box 33, Folder 546)
  - Parking lot (Box 33, Folder 547)
  - Payne Whitney Gym, 1956, undated (Box 33, Folder 548)
  - Peabody Museum
    - African Collection, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 549)
    - "Centennial", 1966 (Box 33, Folder 550)
    - Circus Animals, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 551)
    - Dinosaur Expedition, 1954-1968 (Box 33, Folder 552)
    - Diorama, 1958, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 553)
    - Dunbar, Carl O., 1959 (Box 33, Folder 554)
    - Egypt, 1960-1965 (Box 33, Folder 555)
    - Extension, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 556)
    - Fossils, 1963-1971 (Box 33, Folder 557)
    - General, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 558)
    - Gilbert Alaskan Bear, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 559)
    - Invertebrates, 1965-1968 (Box 34, Folder 560)
    - Lull, Richard S., Paleontology, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 561)
    - Natural History Murals, 1953-1976 (Box 34, Folder 562)
    - New Guinea, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 563)
    - Paynter Expedition, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 564)
    - "Reptiles", 1966 (Box 34, Folder 565)
    - Ripley, S. Dillon, 1951-1964 (Box 34, Folder 566)
    - Students, Equipment (Box 34, Folder 567)
    - Turtles, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 568)
    - Vases, theft of, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 569)
    - Zoology, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 570)
  - Peace Corps
    - 1968, undated (Box 34, Folder 571)
    - Program for Lawyers, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 572)
  - Pennsylvania State University, dormitories, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 573)
  - Personnel
    - Awards, 1950-1966 (Box 34, Folder 574 - 576)
    - Employees' Union, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 577)
    - Retirements, 1953-1966 (Box 35, Folder 578)
  - Phelps Gate (Box 35, Folder 579)
  - Phi Gamma Delta (Box 35, Folder 580)
  - Philosophy, activities of Paul Weiss, 1961-1969 (Box 35, Folder 581)
  - Photography in America 1850-1965 display (Box 35, Folder 582)
  - Lectures
    - A-Cht (Box 30, Folder 485)
    - Chubb Fellows (Box 30, Folder 486 - 488)
    - Chv-E (Box 30, Folder 489)
    - F-Z (Box 31, Folder 490 - 492)
  - Physical Education (Box 35, Folder 583)
  - Physics
    - Atomic Research Laboratory, 1952-1954 (Box 35, Folder 584)
    - Cosmic Rays, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 585)
    - Electron Adapter, 1953-1960 (Box 35, Folder 586)
    - Equipment, 1963-1964 (Box 35, Folder 587)
    - Faculty, 1961-1968 (Box 35, Folder 588 - 589)
    - Heavy-Ion Accelerator, 1951-1961 (Box 36, Folder 590)
    - Heavy-Particle Accelerator, 1954-1956 (Box 36, Folder 591)
    - "Proton" Accelerator, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 592)
    - Radiation, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 593)
    - Second Sound (Box 36, Folder 594)
    - Separator, Beam, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 595)
    - Students, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 596)
    - Uranium Project, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 597)
    - Van De Graaff Accelerator "Emperor", 1963-1971 (Box 36, Folder 598 - 599)
  - Pickets, CORE (Congress on Racial Equality) (Box 36, Folder 600)
  - Pierson-Sage Square Area, 1954-1960 (Box 37, Folder 601)
  - Pinnell, Pat, cartoons (Box 37, Folder 602)
  - Pizza, Naples Restaurant (Box 37, Folder 603)
  - Plane Crash -- Seattle, 1940s (Box 37, Folder 604)
  - Police, University, 1958-1970 (Box 37, Folder 605)
  - Political
    - Campaign, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 606)
    - Science, 1955-1963 (Box 37, Folder 607)
    - Union (Box 37, Folder 608)
  - Pollution (Box 37, Folder 609)
  - Poverty (Box 37, Folder 610)
  - Presidents of Yale
    - Angell, James (Box 37, Folder 611)
    - Brewster, Kingman Jr.
      - Election, 1963, undated (Box 37, Folder 612)
      - Family, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 613)
      - Formal and Informal, 1964-1975 (Box 37, Folder 614)
      - General, 1933-1969 (Box 37, Folder 615)
      - Inauguration, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 616)
    - Dwight, Timothy, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 617)
    - General (Box 37, Folder 618)
    - Seymour, Charles, 1949-1964 (Box 38, Folder 619 - 620)
  - Prince Street School (Box 38, Folder 621)
  - Princeton (Box 38, Folder 622)
  - Princeton Eating Clubs (Box 38, Folder 623)
  - Prom, 1965-1966 (Box 38, Folder 624)
  - Prometheus, sculpture (Box 38, Folder 625)
  - Pro-Musica Ensemble, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 626)
  - Properties, 1955-1958 (Box 38, Folder 627)
  - Provost, 1957-1964 (Box 38, Folder 628)
  - Psychology
    - Undated (Box 38, Folder 629)
    - Miles, Walter R., 1953 (Box 38, Folder 630)
  - Public Health Conference, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 631)
  - "Pundits" (Box 38, Folder 632)
  - Quakers (Box 38, Folder 633)
  - Quality Grocery (Box 38, Folder 634)
  - Racing of toy cars (Box 38, Folder 635)
  - Racoon coats, Class of 1950-1957 (Box 38, Folder 636)
  - Recycling (Box 38, Folder 637)
  - Refugees, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 638)
  - Registration, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 639)
  - Religion, 1949, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 640)
  - Rent strike (Box 38, Folder 641)
  - Repertory Theatre, Yale, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 642)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps (ROTC)
    - Air Science Tactics, 1953-1957 (Box 38, Folder 643)
    - Combined Staffs, 1954-1963 (Box 39, Folder 644)
    - Military Science Tactics, 1949-1968 (Box 39, Folder 645 - 646)
    - Naval Science, 1950-1960s (Box 39, Folder 647)
  - Restaurants (Box 39, Folder 648)
  - Revivalists, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 649)
  - Rheingold Girls, 1962-1964 (Box 39, Folder 650)
  - Riot (Box 39, Folder 651)
  - Rochdale House, Co-op living (Box 39, Folder 652)
  - Rock Music (Box 40, Folder 653)
  - Rolling Stones, singing group (Box 40, Folder 654)
  - Russian
    - Chorus (Box 40, Folder 655)
    - Club (Box 40, Folder 656)
    - Visitors (Box 40, Folder 657)
  - Sailing, Hoyt, Norris D. (Box 40, Folder 658)
  - St. Elmo's, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 659)
  - "Scholars of the House Program", 1949-1956 (Box 40, Folder 660)
  - Scholarships
    - 1950-1973 (Box 40, Folder 661 - 662)
    - 1951-1969 (Box 40, Folder 663)
  - Schools
    - Art and Architecture
      - 1968-1971 (Box 40, Folder 664)
      - Building, 1953-1963 (Box 41, Folder 665 - 666)
      - Faculty, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 667)
      - Fellowships, 1950-1958 (Box 41, Folder 668)
      - General, 1952-1968 (Box 41, Folder 669 - 670)
      - General, 1952-1968 (Box 42, Folder 671)
      - Sizer, Theodore, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 672)
      - Betsy Ross Nursery, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 673)
    - Divinity
      - 1969 (Box 42, Folder 674)
      - Bible Revision Committee, 1950-1953 (Box 42, Folder 675)
      - Convocations, 1952-1962 (Box 42, Folder 676)
      - Deans, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 677)
      - Faculty and students, 1954-1962 (Box 42, Folder 678)
      - General, 1952-1954 (Box 42, Folder 679)
      - Lectures, 1950-1953 (Box 42, Folder 680)
      - Library, 1954-1957 (Box 43, Folder 681)
      - "Master Plan", 1955-1957 (Box 43, Folder 682)
      - Radio/TV, 1953-1954 (Box 43, Folder 683)
      - Religious Service, Jazz, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 684)
      - "Students-in-Industry", 1952 (Box 43, Folder 685)
      - World Council of Churches, 1954-1957 (Box 43, Folder 686)
    - Drama
      - Undated (Box 43, Folder 687)
      - O'Neill, Eugene (Box 43, Folder 688)
      - Productions, 1949-1966 (Box 43, Folder 689)
      - Productions, 1949-1966 (Box 44, Folder 690 - 691)
      - Rolling Theater (Box 44, Folder 692)
      - Smith, Boyd M., portrait, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 693)
      - Sound and lighting, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 694)
      - Students in classes, 1948-1955 (Box 44, Folder 695)
      - Visitors, 1948-1964 (Box 44, Folder 696)
      - Yale Film Association, Paul Newman, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 697)
    - Engineering
      - Applied science
        - Becton Center, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 698)
        - Centennial, 1952-1967 (Box 45, Folder 699)
        - Deans, past and present, 1948-1961 (Box 45, Folder 700)
        - Faculty, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 701)
      - Chemical Engineering
        - "Atomic Garbage", 1955 (Box 45, Folder 702)
        - Equipment, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 703)
        - Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation, Olin Lecture Series, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 704)
        - Petroleum Industry 100th Anniversary, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 705)
        - Salt water to fresh water conversion, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 706)
        - Students, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 707)
      - Civil Engineering
        - Early classes, 1852 (Box 45, Folder 708)
        - Miscellaneous, 1949-1953 (Box 45, Folder 709)
        - Sewerage System, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 710)
        - "Slingshot", 1955 (Box 45, Folder 711)
      - Electrical Engineering
        - Analog computer, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 712)
        - Dunham Laboratory, 1954-1963 (Box 45, Folder 713)
        - "Microwave Theory and Technique", 1954 (Box 45, Folder 714)
        - Servomechanism, 1940-1952 (Box 45, Folder 715)
      - Electrical-Mechanical -- extras (Box 45, Folder 716)
      - Fund, 1955-1956 (Box 46, Folder 717)
      - Industry Advisory Council, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 718)
      - Mechanical
        - Jet Engine, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 719)
        - Safety measures, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 720)
        - Wind Tunnel, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 721)
        - Wohlenberg, W. J., 1952 (Box 46, Folder 722)
      - Study Committee, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 723)
      - Summer Camp at Old Lyme, 1950, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 724)
      - Women, foreign students, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 725)
    - Forestry
      - Anniversary, 50th, 1950s (Box 46, Folder 726)
      - Chinese Technicians (Box 46, Folder 727)
      - Deans, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 728)
      - Equipment, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 729)
      - Expansion Campaign, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 730)
      - Environmental Studies, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 731)
      - Fellowships and Scholarships, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 732)
      - Forest Products Research Association, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 733)
      - Gifts, Grants, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 734)
      - Greeley Memorial Laboratory, 1959-1962 (Box 47, Folder 735)
      - Industrial Forestry, 1955-1965 (Box 47, Folder 736)
      - Interiors, 1961-1964 (Box 47, Folder 737)
      - Lectures, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 738)
      - Research Projects, 1963-1968 (Box 47, Folder 739)
      - Sage Hall, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 740)
      - State Park and Forest Commission, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 741)
      - Students and Faculty, 1952-1965 (Box 47, Folder 742)
      - Summer Camp, Litchfield, CT, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 743)
    - Graduate
      - Alumni, 1965-1968 (Box 47, Folder 744)
      - Connecticut Science Teachers Association Conference, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 745)
      - Cross, Wilbur Medal, 1966-1969 (Box 47, Folder 746)
      - Faculty, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 747)
      - Foreign Area Studies, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 748)
      - Master of Arts Teaching Program
        - Alumni Reunion, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 749)
        - Elementary School French, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 750)
        - "Swahili", 1952 (Box 48, Folder 751)
        - Teacher Training, 1954-1959 (Box 48, Folder 752)
        - Yale-North Haven Summer Session, 1960-1962 (Box 48, Folder 753)
      - PhD Centennial, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 754)
    - Law
      - Undated (Box 48, Folder 755)
      - Alumni Day, 1959-1973 (Box 48, Folder 756)
      - Alumnus, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 757)
      - Barristers' Union, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 758)
      - Chinese Law Course, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 759)
      - Deans, 1954-1955 (Box 49, Folder 760)
      - Deans Shulman and Pike, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 761)
      - Faculty and Students, 1939-1963 (Box 49, Folder 762)
      - Foreign students, 1952-1953 (Box 49, Folder 763)
      - Forum, Yale (Box 49, Folder 764)
      - General Mills meeting, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 765)
      - Interiors, 1956-1961 (Box 49, Folder 766)
      - Journal, 1948-1954 (Box 49, Folder 767)
      - Lecturers, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 768)
      - Moot Court, 1947-1951 (Box 49, Folder 769)
      - Portrait Presentation, 1950-1956 (Box 49, Folder 770)
      - Seabury Prize (Box 49, Folder 771)
      - Students, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 772)
      - Traffic Court Conference, 1957-1961 (Box 49, Folder 773)
      - Two-way Fellowship (Box 49, Folder 774)
      - Visitors, 1954-1968 (Box 49, Folder 775)
    - Medical
      - Affiliations, Hospital, Stamford-St. Joseph's-Yale, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 776)
      - Alumni, 1954-1968 (Box 49, Folder 777)
      - Anatomy
        - 1947-1962 (Box 50, Folder 778)
        - Biochemistry Laboratory, 1957 (Box 50, Folder 779)
        - Burr, Dr. Harold Saxton, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 780)
        - Mice, Strong, Dr. Leonell, Circa 1950 (Box 50, Folder 781)
        - Polentiometer, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 782)
        - Seminar, 1957 (Box 50, Folder 783)
      - Animal Colony, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 784)
      - Anniversary, 150th, 1960-1961 (Box 50, Folder 785)
      - Arbovirus Research Unit, Lassa Fever, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 786)
      - Bacteriology, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 787)
      - Biological Laboratory, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 788)
      - Cancer research, 1949, undated (Box 50, Folder 789)
      - Child Study Center, 1954-1970 (Box 50, Folder 790)
      - Child, Jane Coffin Fund, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 791)
      - Clinical Medicine (Box 50, Folder 792)
      - Connecticut Mental Health Center, 1964-1966 (Box 51, Folder 793)
      - Courses, 1950-1969 (Box 51, Folder 794 - 795)
      - Deans, Berliner, Dr. Robert W., 1973 (Box 51, Folder 796)
      - Epidemiology and Public Health
        - 1952-1966 (Box 51, Folder 797 - 798)
        - Rockefeller Virus Laboratories, 1962-1964 (Box 51, Folder 799)
      - Fousek Memorial Library, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 800)
      - Gesell Institute of Child Development, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 801)
      - Gifts and Grants, 1958-1963 (Box 51, Folder 802)
      - Harkness, Mary S., Auditorium, 1959 (Box 51, Folder 803)
      - Harkness, Edward S., Hall, 1954-1962 (Box 52, Folder 804)
      - Historical data, 1951-1958 (Box 52, Folder 805)
      - Hunter Radiation Therapy Center, 1957-1966 (Box 52, Folder 806)
      - Internal Medicine, 1963-1964 (Box 52, Folder 807)
      - Joint diseases, 1963-1964 (Box 52, Folder 808)
      - Klatskin, Gerald, M.D. Presentation of oil painting, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 809)
      - Laboratories, 1963-1966 (Box 52, Folder 810)
      - Lecturers, 1956-1966 (Box 52, Folder 811)
      - Library, 1949-1960 (Box 52, Folder 812)
      - Medical Genetics Clinic, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 813)
      - "Medicine", Technology, 1958-1962 (Box 52, Folder 814)
      - Microbiology, 1952-1958 (Box 52, Folder 815)
      - Micro-projector (Box 53, Folder 816)
      - Miscellaneous, 1965-1973 (Box 53, Folder 817)
      - Neurology, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 818)
      - Newborn Care Center, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 819)
      - Newborn Special Care Unit, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 820)
      - Nutrition, cats on artificial diet (Box 53, Folder 821)
      - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1949-1968 (Box 53, Folder 822)
      - Occupational Medicine and Hygiene Advisory Committee, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 823)
      - Opthomology, 1957-1964 (Box 53, Folder 824)
      - Otologic Laboratory, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 825)
      - Otolaryngology, 1956-1957 (Box 53, Folder 826)
      - Pathology, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 827)
      - Pediatrics
        - 1956-1963 (Box 53, Folder 828)
        - Spectrophotometer (Box 53, Folder 829)
      - Perinatal Research Center, 1956-1965 (Box 53, Folder 830)
      - Pharmacology, 1953-1957 (Box 54, Folder 831)
      - Physics, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 832)
      - Physiological Chemistry
        - Cancer, Dr. Abraham White (Box 54, Folder 833)
        - Hormones-proteins, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 834)
      - Physiology
        - Aeromedical Research (Box 54, Folder 835)
        - Delgado, Dr. Jose, 1952-1967 (Box 54, Folder 836)
        - Fulton, Dr. John F., 1952 (Box 54, Folder 837)
        - Lamport, Dr. Harold (Box 54, Folder 838)
        - Physiological Chemistry, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 839)
        - "Plasmin", 1957 (Box 54, Folder 840)
      - Poliomyelitis Research, 1952-1960 (Box 55, Folder 841)
      - Portraits, 1959-1967 (Box 55, Folder 842)
      - Preventive medicine (Box 55, Folder 843)
      - Psychiatry, 1953-1963 (Box 55, Folder 844)
      - Psychology, 1963-1966 (Box 55, Folder 845)
      - Scholarships, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 846)
      - Staff, 1967-1969 (Box 55, Folder 847)
      - Students, 1951-1961 (Box 55, Folder 848)
      - Surgery
        - "Bone Engineering", 1955-1956 (Box 55, Folder 849)
        - Cardiovascular Unit, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 850)
        - Guthrie Professorship, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 851)
        - Humane Research Law, 1958-1963 (Box 55, Folder 852)
        - Miscellaneous, 1965-1969 (Box 55, Folder 853)
        - Tumor Clinic (Box 55, Folder 854)
      - Tommy Memorial Fund, 1953-1955 (Box 55, Folder 855)
      - Urology (Box 56, Folder 856)
      - Visitors, 1954-1959 (Box 56, Folder 857)
      - Winerman, Dr. E. Richard Memorial Reading Room Dedication, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 858)
      - World Health Organization (WHO) Serum Bank, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 859)
      - Yale-New Haven Medical Center, 1954-1967 (Box 56, Folder 860)
    - Music
      - Awards and presentations, 1962-1964 (Box 56, Folder 861)
      - Bartholomew, Marshall, "First 150 Years of Music at Yale", 1955 (Box 56, Folder 862)
      - Centennial, 1954-1955 (Box 56, Folder 863)
      - Center of Musical Instruments, 1952-1963 (Box 56, Folder 864)
      - Electronic Music Studio, 1962-1965 (Box 56, Folder 865)
      - Exhibition of rare books, 1953-1961 (Box 56, Folder 866)
      - Faculty, 1949-1966 (Box 56, Folder 867)
      - International Federation of Music Students, 1951 (Box 57, Folder 868)
      - Ives, Charles E., 1954-1956 (Box 57, Folder 869)
      - Jackson, John Herrick, Library, 1955-1964 (Box 57, Folder 870)
      - Merovingian Bible, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 871)
      - Musical sounds, IBM computer, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 872)
      - Norfolk Summer School, 1950-1965 (Box 57, Folder 873)
      - Sprague Hall Library, 1954-1964 (Box 57, Folder 874)
      - Students, 1952-1963 (Box 57, Folder 875 - 876)
    - Nursing
      - Anniversary, 25th, 1949-1951 (Box 57, Folder 877)
      - Dormitories, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 878)
      - Faculty, 1964-1968 (Box 57, Folder 879)
      - First male student, 1954-1955 (Box 58, Folder 880)
      - Obstetrics, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 881)
      - Pediatrics, 1952-1955 (Box 58, Folder 882)
      - Projects, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 883)
      - Visitors, 1952-1960 (Box 58, Folder 884)
    - Sheffield Scientific School, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 885)
  - Science, computer, laser, space, 1964-1966 (Box 58, Folder 886)
  - Sculpture (Box 58, Folder 887)
  - Secret Societies (Box 58, Folder 888)
  - Seminars
    - 1967, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 889 - 890)
    - Directed Studies (Box 58, Folder 891)
  - Service Bureau -- condition of rooms, 1955-1956 (Box 58, Folder 892)
  - Service examination, 1951 (Box 58, Folder 893)
  - Seven Springs Farm, 1973-1976 (Box 58, Folder 894)
  - Shakespeare
    - Crawford Collection (Box 59, Folder 895)
    - Elizabethan Playhouse, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 896)
    - Festival, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 897)
    - First Folio, 1623, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 898)
    - Henry IV, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 899)
    - Institute, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 900)
    - "Much Ado About Nothing", 1958 (Box 59, Folder 901)
    - Poems, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 902)
    - Research, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 903)
  - Sha-Na-Na, Bob Slattery, singing group (Box 59, Folder 904)
  - Shape of the Future, poster (Box 59, Folder 905)
  - Sit-a-thon, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 906)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 59, Folder 907)
  - Social Science Center (Box 59, Folder 908)
  - Sociology, 1949-1968 (Box 59, Folder 909 - 910)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference, staff member, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 911)
  - Spring (Box 59, Folder 912)
  - Squash (Box 59, Folder 913)
  - Stealing (Box 59, Folder 914)
  - Sterling Memorial Library
    - 1742 Library and overcrowding, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 915 - 916)
    - American Literature Collection, 1958 (Box 60, Folder 917)
    - Babylonian Collection, 1952-1961 (Box 60, Folder 918)
    - Bay Psalm Book, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 919)
    - Benjamin Franklin Collection, 1954-1969 (Box 60, Folder 920 - 921)
    - Bibliographical Press Room, 1947-1955 (Box 60, Folder 922)
    - Bollinger Committee, 1950-1955 (Box 60, Folder 923)
    - Boswell Papers (Box 60, Folder 924)
    - "Canterbury Tales", woodcut, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 925)
    - Cataloging (Box 60, Folder 926)
    - Coe Collection of Western Americana, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 927)
    - Collections, exhibitions, 1965-1968 (Box 60, Folder 928)
    - Colt Press Collection, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 929)
    - Conrad Papers, 1957 (Box 61, Folder 930)
    - Constance Missal Leaf, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 931)
    - "Constat" Luwig, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 932)
    - "Contoura" Ludwig, 1949, undated (Box 61, Folder 933)
    - Crane Collection, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 934)
    - Cross Campus addition, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 935)
    - Daly, Ewin, Exhibition, Circa 1957 (Box 61, Folder 936)
    - Davis, John W., Collection, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 937)
    - Dickens, Charles, Collection, 1942-1962 (Box 61, Folder 938)
    - Doolittle, Hilda (H.D.), 1956 (Box 61, Folder 939)
    - Elihu Yale documents, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 940)
    - English Literature, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 941)
    - Far Eastern Collection, 1952-1956 (Box 61, Folder 942)
    - Five million mark in volumes, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 943)
    - Ginter, Henry, Binding Department, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 944)
    - Great Charter of 1638, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 945)
    - Givinnet, Button, document, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 946)
    - Historical Sound Recordings Program, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 947)
    - Johnson, James Weldon, Collection, 1950-1959 (Box 61, Folder 948)
    - Johnson, Samuel, Collection, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 949)
    - Joyce, James, Collection, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 950)
    - Judaica Collection, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 951)
    - Latin American Literature Collection, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 952)
    - Lewis and Clark Papers, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 953)
    - Librarians, 1965-1972 (Box 61, Folder 954)
    - Lincoln, Abraham, Collection, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 955)
    - Literary Forgeries, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 956)
    - Mann, Thomas, Collection, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 957)
    - Map Collection, 1950-1962 (Box 62, Folder 958)
    - Medieval manuscripts, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 959)
    - Memorabilia Room, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 960)
    - Nathan, Robert, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 961)
    - Numismatic Collection, 1953-1970 (Box 62, Folder 962)
    - O'Neill, Eugene Collection, 1956-1962 (Box 62, Folder 963)
    - Paine, Thomas, Collection, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 964)
    - Papyri Collection, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 965)
    - "Perush Iyob", 1954 (Box 62, Folder 966)
    - Poe, Edgar Allen, Collection, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 967)
    - Political Campaign Exhibition, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 968)
    - Pound, Ezra, Papers, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 969)
    - Propaganda Leaflets Collection, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 970)
    - Rare Book Room, miscellaneous, 1952-1958 (Box 62, Folder 971)